You tested negative.
お前陰性あったなぁ
Hey.
なぁ
Shall we try Osaki today?
今日大崎のこともチャレンジしよっか?
Oh, I don't like it.
え、嫌です
why?
なんで?
I don't dislike it.
嫌とかないよ
Don't you understand if you keep quiet?
黙っててわかんないの?
What should I do?
どうする?
I don't want to reply.
返信したくないです
What the hell?
なんてなんて?
I don't want to reply.
返信したくないです
Don't want to reply?
返信したくないの?
I don't think I've heard of that.
そんなの聞いてないみたいな
What should I do?
どうする?
Come up with a defense.
弁護出して
Yeah, would you like me to take it out?
ええ、出してもらう?
At this point, I'll do what you like.
この時お前好きなのやってやるよ
Let's learn many shapes today too.
今日も沢山の形と習おうね
Yeah.
うん
Let's confirm the pregnancy.
妊娠確定しよう
Yeah.
うん
Shall I confirm my pregnancy?
妊娠確定しよっか?
hey?
ね?
Yeah.
うん
As someone like me who hates having children, I feel like they're looking at me.
子づくり嫌がってる俺には、 こっちを見てきてるみたいだけど
Yeah.
うん
What's wrong with this?
どうしたのこれ?
It's crowded.
人ひいてるでな
Yeah.
うん
It's soaking wet.
びしょびしょだね
Yeah.
うん
This is where the baby comes out.
こっから赤ちゃん出てくるんだ
Have you decided on a name?
名前決めた?
What should I do?
どうしよっか?
What should I name my mother?
母ちゃんの名前何しよっか?
Yeah.
うん
What should I do?
どうする?
Yeah.
うん
Would you like to have the same name as me?
俺と同じ名前しよっか?
Yeah.
うん
Do you prepare your father's bamboo?
お父さんの竹仕込みする?
Yeah.
うん
What should I do?
どうしよっか?
Yeah.
うん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Hmm.
う ーん
It's really close.
ほんとすぐすぐだね
Yeah.
うん
Hey, Eno?
ね えの?
Yeah.
うん
They're all big, aren't they?
全部大きいじゃんか
Hey.
ねえ
I'll take the trouble to do it.
せっかくだしよ
Yeah.
うん
How can this remain?
どうやって残るのこれ?
Hey?
ねえ?
How can this remain?
どうやって残るのこれ?
Shall I go home naked today?
今日裸で帰ろか?
I don't like it.
嫌です
Do you not like it?
嫌なの?
Nice boobs.
いいおっぱいだね
Yeah.
うん
Shall I take it for now?
とりあえず取っちゃおうか
Hey, come on.
ねえ、おいで
Yeah.
うん
Same hit?
同じ当たる?
happy.
うれしい
Apparently I'm planning on doing a 3 piece today.
今日 俺なんか3ピースする予定らしいよ
Is it 3 pieces?
3ピースか
Yeah.
うん
That's nice.
いいですね
Which one should I start with?
どっちからする?
Will you put my dick in?
俺のチンポ入れる?
Let's confirm the pregnancy now.
もう、妊娠確定しちゃおうね
I don't like it.
嫌です
picture?
え?
I don't like it.
嫌です
If I cum, I'll probably get pregnant.
俺が中出したらだいたい妊娠するよ
Yeah.
うん
It was tough because everyone was so hungry.
み んな腹ましちゃって大変だったね、
Kozaki.
小崎
Ah, I don't know.
あ、知らないですね
I've had a crush on girls since I was in first year of middle school.
俺、中一の時から女の子腹ましたからね
I can get back to it later.
この後回せれちゃうね
Yeah.
うん
Kosaki, the person you like is fine.
小崎、お前の好きな人いいぞ
Looks like you'll do a good job today, Kosaki.
今日いい子供できそうだな、小崎、
you.
お前
It feels good.
いい感じですね
For a healthy child to be born.
元気な子ちゃん生まれる子に
That's fine.
いいじゃん
A healthy baby will be born.
元気な子ちゃん生まれるね
Yeah.
うん
Wasn't it good?
良 かった じゃん?
良かったじゃん?
Nice boobs.
いいおっぱいだね
It's true that I'm on my knees.
確かにおつむいなってほら
It's a wrap.
おつむいなりなほら
No, but.
ダメだけど
Push it out.
押しつき出して
Nice ass, really.
いいお尻だね、本当に
Shall we do Adal today?
今日アダルやっちゃおうか?
Push it out more, properly.
もっと押しつき出して、ちゃんと
Yeah.
うん
It's not bad, I'll do that.
ダメじゃない、そのやだれたらしちゃう
I'll be angry.
怒るよ
Yeah.
うん
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさいよ
yes.
はい
Yeah.
うん
Raise your feet directly above you.
足真上に上げて
Which one do you want?
どっちが欲しい?
boy and girl.
男の子と女の子
Yeah.
うん
Which should I choose?
どっちにしよっか?
Yeah.
うん
I can't choose which one to go with though.
どっちにしようかって選べないけどね
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
Yeah.
うん
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
Yeah.
うん
Which one?
どっちどっち?
I really hate it.
すごい嫌がります
Look here.
こっち見て
Yeah.
うん
quickly.
早く
What should I do?
どうしよう?
Yeah.
うん
What should I do?
どうしよう?
Already perch properly, myself.
もうちゃんとパーチして、自分で
Spread it out and see.
なんか 広げて、ほら
Seems understandable.
わかりそうです
How much does it cost to live for two days?
二日に暮らしたって、どんくらいするの?
How much does it cost?
どんくらいするの?
Next, let's take a video of the test.
次、検査の動画撮ろうか
Yeah.
うん
If it turns out to be positive, we'll win.
無事陽性が出たら、俺らの勝ちやな
It's tough.
大変だね
What should I do?
どうする?
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよです
I don't dislike it though.
嫌とかないけどね
Yeah.
うん
Well then, I'll go home.
じゃあ、帰るから
see you.
またね
Yeah.
うん
Come again tomorrow.
また明日来いよ
yes.
はい
It's the Kitajima group's pet.
北島グループのペットなんだ
It is a pet of the Kitajima group.
北島グループのペットです
Yeah, see you then.
うん、じゃあね
bye bye.
バイバイ
Bye bye?
バイバイは?
Smile and wave.
ニコニコ、手振って
bye bye.
バイバイ
See you then.
じゃあね
Then please go ahead.
じゃあどうぞ
Thank you for your hard work.
お疲れさまでした